Seeno, gargal channel, go-go!
Yes, so today, I would like to play the Laila game with these members!
Raira!
Lia! I would like to play the lia game!
One more time!
I would like to play the lia game!
Yeah!
You're not too sure!
Yes, what is it? The Lia game.
The Lia game is a game in which, since there are six of us today, we're going to split into two teams of three and three.
One of the three is doing something.
To see through that, you know.
To give it up.
You have a dog if it's obvious.
I'm going to find out who's really loving this, who's really holding it.
Two people don't have it, and then they get this look on their face.
It's a long-distance confrontation.
That's right.
So, the three of us will be grouped with these three.
Gupta.
That's right.
Okay, so we'll pick the best high school.
Best high school?
You're right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. High school.
I want high school. I want high school.
First, Goo, Gemin, Pooi!
First pitch.
Yes! Yes!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
First to attack.
What?
First to act.
Whoever wins gets to go first.
I thought the winner was the high school.
That's what you said.
They're all coming.
My head's a little far in the clouds.
See you the day after the February show.
We're doing our best.
So we are the first to attack!
We're wearing costumes by D-Holic this time!
Yuzu, are you sure you can do this?
Oh! Did you say it as an act?
Acting.
Are you confident?
Because you have a dog.
But think about it.
The whole team over there has a dog.
That's true.
That's right.
We're all in trouble.
What are we supposed to do?
You don't know what to do if you touch a dog. Not to begin with.
But it's a doll.
It's got a voice, right?
So I just have to match it to Yuzu?
Well, Yuzu is giving it to me.
I'll do it.
Here we go.
I can't see you.
Yes, I said you can't see me.
Grandpa.
Okay, okay.
This is bad.
I wonder who it is.
Here we go.
You're all going that way, aren't you?
You're coming over there, aren't you?
So cute!
So cute.
No way, guys.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
I'll bring it to you.
Question time?
I have no idea.
Momochan's eyes seemed to be shifting.
I see. In what position do you hold it?
But you hold it with your hand, so when your hand moves, you look at it.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's kind of violent, isn't it?
The type that moves its hands.
I see.
Look at the hand, because it's held with the hand.
Because the hands are moving.
That's right, that's right.
I see. I understand.
I felt like you two were standing way down here.
I thought so.I thought.
I don't know if that's suspicious or true.
Certainly.
But personally, I think Yuzu
I think Yuzu is the type of person who talks like a baby to her pets.
That's amazing.
It is.
I think she's making it her home.
I wonder if she really has one.
I see.
Here we go.
Oh, poor baby.
He's so cool.
Did you care about what I just said?
Is that part of the plan?
There you go.
No?
Killer?
Look who's here.
Killer.
What's the right answer?
Jan!
Yeah!
I feel sorry for you.
Go on.
I've got a plan.
I wonder if I can actually
I wonder if I can see it.
Look at the knees of those who don't have it.
It's cute.
That's possible.
But the point is...
I'm gonna make you squeeze it, just to be sure.
Because it can't be true.
It can't be.
Can I turn it around and pull out the baby?
No way.
You're so cute.
Can I? That's good.
It's okay.
Here you go.
Please, sit down.
Sit down.
Okay, now, close your eyes for a second to shuffle.
Look down and close your eyes.
Okay.
All right, let's get started.
Cute, cute, cute, cute.
Cute, cute, cute, so cute.
So cute. So cute. So cute.
I see. Um...
Oh, I see.
I see... I see... I see...
I was worried about Misaki's eyes. They were so blurry.
She's so vivacious. She's too slow to look at you.
What are you looking at?
I think it's clear. My gut says it's clear.
Oh, wow!
Misaki, can I get another one?
I'm gonna get in trouble for that face.
All right, let's get started.
That's cute. That's cute. That's cute.
Both of your hands are up.
Don't you hear that?
I know! I know! I know! I got it! I got it!
Okay, okay, okay!
You have to say it.
So, um...
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't think I'll do it again.
I think I'm going to cry.
Where are you getting this from?
What's the matter with you, Kiritz?
Soyan-chan, with both hands now.
Let's celebrate.
Okay, Claire.
Then our answer is...
Claire.
Ta-da!
Yay!
But it's irresponsible.
Why is that?
But we both did it.
Yes, we did.
One on one.One on one.
Next game?
Quiz.
You're not gonna make me do this again, are you?
You know what I mean.
I'll start with one-on-one.
Thank you for having me.
Thank you very much.
I don't know about that.
I'm going to go out on a limb here.
Kiritz's.
Wait a minute.
One time
Anumai.
Wait a minute.
Yuzu.
We'll do our best to cover for you.
That's fine.
That's a lot of responsibility.
Oh, no.
Are you sitting down already? I'll sit down and we'll start.
All right, open it up.
Not yet.
I'm sitting.
Oh, go on.
What, what, what, what?
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
Somo-chan, are you sitting on my neck?
I don't know.
Maybe it's a dare.
But we're all just as unstable as you.
We're all a little unstable right now.
Like this.
But Kira's sitting here.
Kira, Kira.
I'll close my eyes.
Blow it out.
Oh, my God!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Close your eyes.
Yes, that's OK.
So it's Momochan's neck.
But Momochan...
It's so obvious.
Momochan has a lot of muscles.
Yes, she does.
She's so heavy.
It was intentional.
But, you know, after that, when she said, "Stop it!
It was really nice.
Hey, stop it, neck.
Can I go on one more time?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Who's not sitting down?
Momochan.
The correct answer is...
It's Yuzu.
Oh, my God!
How do you fold the neck?
This is how you put your strength into your body.
The muscles come here.
I see.
Do it like that.
Oh, my God!
Seriously, look at your stance.
Oh, my God.
I know, right?
It's so high. Your hands are so high.
Good job, guys!
Oh, my God, I'm so frustrated!
Everyone around here is so good.
I want to cover.
That's great.
Okay, let's move on.
I'm going home.
The first one guessed it.
He said, "Boo!" He said, "Boo!
You can't even see the shoulder cut.
I see what you mean.
That's right.
You mean this?
Just the face.
Get closer.
The other way around?
I can't see.
That's the rule.
We don't have to do anything in the air.
It's all right.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
We can feel each other's swaying.
You're so close.
You guys should try it together, up close.
What kind of shaking?
The shaking is the work.
Go on.
Oh, but I don't know.
But the person who's sitting on it is going to be a little lower.
Oh, okay, look again.
Come on, let's do it again.
Okay, okay, okay.
Here we go.
Ready?
It's a little tricky, isn't it?
No cheating?
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm?
I thought so while I was playing jaconquies.
It's like, "Pull, pull, pull, pull, pull.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Are you okay?
I'm smiling right now.
It's the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
You don't look like this.
You don't have muscles.
I'll never do it.
I can't do it.
Lately...
I'm doing Cookies.
You all did Cookies?
No, wait, just one.
What? Just one?
Just one?
He didn't sit down, did he?
No, no, one person is not sitting.
What?
Is that alcohol?
He's got a really serious look on his face.
Wait a minute.
You're smiling.
I know you're smiling.
What?
He's laughing.
What the fuck just happened?
What's happening? What's happening?
What are you doing?
Is this it?
No, no, no.
Why are you two meeting?
Like this.
I'm coming back.
I'm quitting.
What are you doing?
It's just the two of you, right? We're doing it.
That's why only one of us did it before.
That's right.
I did it.
What's he doing?
They did it.
Like this.
I thought, "What's going on?
I thought he'd be here.
I feel like I'm lying on my head.
Shake it out.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Okay.
All right!
Yes!
Okay, here we go.
Let's get started!
Don't look at the bottom.
I'm shaking it on purpose.
It's shaking.
It's not shaking.
You scared me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on, come on.
Come on, 20 seconds.
Three more seconds.
Hot, hot, hot.
Misaki's not here.
How's it coming?
Souchan, there was a bump here.
It was shaking.It was shaking.
But I don't know about that.
Wait.
The only reason I'm out here like this is because...
Claire is Goody-Two-Shoes.
I told her we should all work together.
Claire asked if I could do it.
You got them all to come forward?
That's great!
Wait a minute.
It's supposed to shake.
For 20 seconds.
I'll be there.
I'm watching you.
We're going together.
Toa's very touchy nose and a little bit of a strong feeling.
It's a little intense.
Is Toa doing it at home?
I've never been.
What do you think?
Well, I think I'll go with Toa for the goodies.
Woo...
Here he comes.
Yeah!
Jump yourself.
Are you okay?
How did you do that once?
Claire did this.
Just up front.
I don't know why it's like that.
They were doing it the first time.
Because they know Toa's pull.
I didn't think I could break it up.
I see what you're getting at.
Next...
Wasabi cream puffs.
I know, I know. It's so loud.
It's an instant reaction.
Which one is it?
Seriously, you from
Can I eat it now?
Can I open my eyes?
Like this, over there.
Yes, ma'am.
Shall we go?
Let's see who's in front of us.
We don't want to miss them.
Here we go!
Magic style.
That way.
You're good.
What? It's not too spicy, is it?
Uma!
Kira looks like tears.
Hey, kun...
They're all here, they're all here.
Everybody, stop drying your eyes.
Is that what I think it is?
You're so smart.
Maybe that's why Kira's so dry.
All the time.
You're right, she's been doing it the whole time.
Hey, man.
It's water.
It's hard.
If it was hard, it would show on the skin a little more.
Momochan is an actress. She does it on purpose.
You think you're good at it?
I don't know.
Actually, I think you're on a timeout.
I'm good with spicy food.
When she ate it, she didn't look pink or teary.
Was I watery?
It would have been easier if Kira had said I was fussy.
Is it possible for something that amazing to happen?
I don't know if I've ever seen anything like that.
I thought about Yuzu first.
On the contrary.
Who do you think?
Yuzu.
Yuzu's the one who's having a hard time.
Really?
Yuzu?
Yuzu is the one who ate the spicy food.
Correct.
It's me.
Yay!
Now we're even, right?
I knew it!
Was it hard?
I feel sick. I feel sick to my stomach.I feel sick. I feel sick to my stomach.
I don't know what to say.
It's not spicy?
It's spicy.
But after swallowing it, this sick feeling is awful.
It's something in my stomach.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Everyone is too good.
Next.
Can we do it?
On the other hand...
Yes.
Yes, yes.
I like it.
Hajime Shacho Ending
Aoi, small unwanted
Aoi, thanks for that.
I'm smiling.
Clock ends
Thank you for watching!
The amount of water is stuck in the container.
Misaki, too. It was a bit of an act.
It was like her nose was twitching.
On purpose?
Misaki, you're burning yourself here, so I'm going to eat something spicy.
Oh...
It's burning now.
Are you okay?
Cut the meat.
We grilled the meat and ate it together.
I was too hungry.
You're so cute.
You can go crayon wasabi.
Thank you very much for today.
-I don't...
I don't know.
-I don't know.
I'd be scared if it wasn't first.
Then you're scared already.
But I don't know. Maybe it's Claire.
It could be Claire.
But you want to go with Claire? I don't know.
Once, once.
Okay, then.
Our guess is...
Claire.
The correct answer is Claire.
Isn't that creepy?
No, it's not.
Oh, my God, I knew it.
Well... the plan was...
We were all supposed to act like we were in pain.
But it didn't work on this guy.
That's why I laughed.
I'll do it.
Can I eat wasabi?
No, I can't.
Well? There you go.
I got it.
I mean, I get it.
No, but I'm thinking Toa.
It's not that I can't eat it, it's not that I don't want to eat the Toa.
I'm just wondering if you're gonna say you don't want to do the clear.
So, clear...
I think they're going to think that I'm going to make them do it.
But I don't think he's going to want to do the clearing.
That's, you know, it's not that I don't want to do it, it's that I can't do it.
I can't do it.
That's great.
Okay, last one.
That's disgusting.
Nice. Disgusting.
I'm sorry.
And that's how it ends.
You have completed all the items, and our team has won.
Thank you very much.
It's really frustrating.
I haven't said much.
You did a great job.
That's the best laugh I've had all day.
It really was the best laugh of the day.
It was fun.
Thank you for watching!
If you thought this video was good, please give it a high rating, comment and subscribe to the channel!
Bye bye!
Bye bye bye.Bye bye bye.